Mark Myance.
>> Welcome back to my channel, Mark My
Finance, where we talk about the latest
in personal finance. Friends, life moves
fast, but when health challenges arise,
financial protection becomes most
important more than ever. Introducing
ICIC Lombard Elevate, a health insurance
plan designed to give you the
confidence, the flexibility, and the
comprehensive healthcare support you
need for protecting your family. And
this is why you need to watch this
video. Medical costs continue to rise
every year. A sudden hospitalization can
impact not just your family but your
health, your wallet and everything and
your financial goals. That's why
choosing the right health insurance plan
is very very essential not just for
emergencies but for long-term peace of
mind. Now let us see some of the
features of ICA Lombard Elevate health
insurance plan so that you can have a
proper decision and how whether you want
to buy this plan or not.
So here are some of the features of ICA
Lombard Ele plan. The summon short goes
all the way starts at five lakhs and
goes all the way up to unlimited cover
unlimited reset benefit which means that
for some of us who want to have an
unlimited experience 100% restoration of
summer show is available and you can
actually convert your plan into an
unlimited plan. The infinite care add-on
rider is what you need to buy to make
this uh unlimited summer show. The power
booster option for all of us who like to
see our summer show doubling every year.
This is a 100% bonus every year without
any cap. For any of us who have
pre-existing diseases like diabetes,
hypertension, amma, obesity, etc., you
can now reduce the waiting period to
just 30 days by buying the jump start
add-on rider. Covers hospitalization of
just 2 hours for eligible daycare
treatments. So unlike some of the other
plans, this is great. It has
prehospization expenses covered up to 90
days and posh hospitalized expense
expenses covered up to 180 days. Now
this policy also covers inpatient
hospitalization, IUS treatment, daycare
procedures, modern-day treatments. So
see friends, this is very very important
today because you might not stay the
whole day in hospital and you might want
to come out very early on. It also
covers biatic surgery, donor expenses, a
domestic ambulance. So you see these are
the other add-ons that are inbuilt and
so domestic ambulance you have you have
maternity also you have maternity for uh
people who want to avail of it and this
is an add-on rider that you can take it
also covers the surrogate mother and the
octite donor expenses up to five lakhs
now there is a if any of you are
worldwide global travelers and you want
to have an optional worldwide cover you
can make this into a global policy now
there is something called claim
protector so add-ons covering non-paid
payable, consumables, and medical items.
These are like syringes, doctor's gowns
and everything. If you want this to be
paid, you need to buy this rider. The
wellness program can give you rewards up
to 30% when you do things like that are
healthy like lifestyle related like
walking and other things. It also has an
optional OPD and durable medical
equipment cover and this is something
you need to read the fine print if you
want to buy. The policy has an inbuilt
sing private AC room eligibility with a
room upgrade modifier is also available.
No disease- wise sublimits on
treatments. Lifelong renewability is
there. Well, the entry age starts at 18
years and the child covered from the 91
days is is possible. There's a large uh
cashless hospital network. Of course,
this is ICA Lombard. So, 10,000 plus
hospitals across India are covered. What
are the other optional benefits that you
can look at to make this policy a little
better? There's a critical illness
cover. There's a personal accident
cover. Then there's an air ambulance
cover. So many of you go trekking in the
mountains and all. If you want to be if
there's an emergency, you need this uh
cover. There's nursing at home. There's
health checkups that you can add.
There's inflation protection. Okay, this
is something I don't recommend, but you
can still investigate and do it. And all
of you are NRIs, there's a discount that
ICA Lombard offers you to make the deal
sweeter. And also there is multi-year
discount. So you can block the pricing
for up to 5 years when you look at
buying this product. Now do consult a
proper financial consultant before you
buy this product and do your own
research. But trust me friends uh this
is Mark my finance and I have been in
the industry for over two decades. I
love putting out these videos so that
all of you can make your own research
make your own decision and any of you
want some help on comparing your
existing health insurance plan or you're
looking at buying something for your
family or in-laws or parents just reach
out on the biller number. Thank you for
watching.
Mark my finance.